Inspired by a true story of survival.
The Lost Bus is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Paul Greengrass.
A determined father risks everything to rescue a dedicated
teacher and her students from a raging wildfire.
Kevin McKay, played by Matthew McConaughey.
Mary Ludwig, played by America Ferrera.
Chief Martinez, played by Yul Vazquez.
Ruby Bishop, played by Ashlie Atkinson.
Linda, played by Kimberli Flores.
Shaun, played by Levi McConaughey.
The Lost Bus is a 2025 American survival drama film directed by Paul Greengrass, who co-wrote the
screenplay with Brad Ingelsby based on the 2021 book Paradise by Lizzie Johnson.
It stars Matthew McConaughey, America Ferrera, Yul Vazquez and Ashlie Atkinson.
The Lost Bus premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 5, 2025, and
received a limited theatrical release in the United States on September 19.
The film made its streaming debut on Apple TV+ on October 3.
It received generally positive reviews, with
critical acclaim for its visual effects.
At the 98th Academy Awards, it was nominated for Best Visual Effects.
The film explores themes of california, based on novel or book, based
on true story, struggle for survival, single father.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.